♪When darkness gathers, flowing like a river♪
♪عندما يتجمع الظلام، يتدفق مثل النهر♪
♪We stand apart at distant ends♪
♪نحن نقف منفصلين في نهايات بعيدة♪
♪Bound by fate, we fight with no way back♪
♪مقيدون بالقدر، نقاتل بلا طريق للعودة♪
♪Once we act, no regrets remain♪
♪بمجرد أن نتصرف، لن يبقى هناك أي ندم♪
♪Defying the looming foreboding♪
♪تحدي النذير الوشيك♪
♪Breaking free from tangled strands♪
♪التحرر من الخيوط المتشابكة♪
♪Lost in the dark, with bullets cold♪
♪ضائع في الظلام، مع الرصاص البارد♪
♪Till all fades away like smoke♪
♪حتى يتلاشى كل شيء مثل الدخان♪
=Hide Games=
=إخفاء الألعاب=
=Episode 14=
=الحلقة 14=
Place your bets, come on, hurry up.
ضع رهاناتك، هيا، أسرع.
Nameless Rookie
مبتدئ بلا اسم
versus the King of Killers.
مقابل ملك القتلة.
You managed to find me.
لقد تمكنت من العثور علي.
Not bad at all.
ليس سيئا على الاطلاق.
Actually, I didn't find you.
في الحقيقة، لم أجدك.
It was Zhang Ahua who found you.
لقد كان تشانغ أهوا هو الذي وجدك.
Zhang Ahua?
تشانغ أهوا؟
Who's that?
من هو الذي؟
The young girl you killed.
الفتاة الصغيرة التي قتلتها.
She's only twenty-one.
إنها في الحادية والعشرين من عمرها فقط.
I came here today
لقد جئت هنا اليوم
to settle this debt for her.
لتسوية هذا الدين لها.
You shouldn't have come.
لا ينبغي لك أن تأتي.
Anywhere else, I'd let you go,
في أي مكان آخر، سأدعك تذهب،
but not here.
ولكن ليس هنا.
This is the place under God's gaze.
هذا هو المكان تحت نظر الله.
You could really die here.
من الممكن أن تموت هنا حقا.
Our plan didn't just fail.
لم تفشل خطتنا فحسب.
It was totally out of control.
لقد كان الأمر خارجا عن السيطرة تماما.
It's my fault he got hurt.
إنه خطئي أنه أصيب.
Don't talk like that.
لا تتحدث هكذا.
I came here hoping
لقد جئت إلى هنا على أمل
we could come up with a plan.
يمكننا أن نتوصل إلى خطة.
I don't have a plan.
ليس لدي خطة.
He doesn't trust me anymore.
إنه لم يعد يثق بي بعد الآن.
And if we do find him, then what?
وإذا وجدناه، ماذا بعد؟
I honestly have no idea.
أنا بصراحة ليس لدي أي فكرة.
I shouldn't have come up with this plan.
لا ينبغي لي أن أتوصل إلى هذه الخطة.
Keep going.
يستمر في التقدم.
I just don't get it.
انا لا أفهم ذلك.
You've got people backing you,
لقد حصلت على الناس يدعمونك،
shielding you.
حمايتك.
I was even told to steer clear of you.
حتى أنني قيل لي أن أبتعد عنك.
But look at you now,
ولكن انظر إليك الآن،
do you really deserve it?
هل تستحق ذلك حقا؟
I was thinking
كنت أفكر
if we manage to find him,
إذا تمكنا من العثور عليه،
we should just tell him the truth.
ينبغي علينا أن نقول له الحقيقة.
No way.
مستحيل.
Absolutely not.
بالتأكيد لا.
He's been through so much.
لقد مر بالكثير.
And his memory hasn't come back.
ولم تعد ذكراه
Right now he's probably
في الوقت الحالي ربما هو
in a highly unstable mental state.
في حالة ذهنية غير مستقرة للغاية.
If he takes another hit,
إذا تلقى ضربة أخرى،
he could totally lose his grip.
كان من الممكن أن يفقد قبضته تمامًا.
What does that mean?
ماذا يعني ذلك؟
It means he'll lose his mind.
وهذا يعني أنه سيفقد عقله.
And develop a protective personality.
وتنمية الشخصية الوقائية.
This another self has no reason.
هذا الذات الأخرى ليس لها سبب.
Its possessiveness and aggression run high.
إنها تتمتع برغبة في التملك والعدوانية بشكل كبير.
If it's not kept in check in time,
إذا لم يتم التحكم فيه في الوقت المناسب،
this second personality
هذه الشخصية الثانية
will slowly consume the host.
سوف تستهلك المضيف ببطء.
Come on, again.
تعال مرة أخرى.
I'll turn everyone who helps you,
سأحول كل من يساعدك،
everyone who likes you,
كل من يحبك
and everyone you like,
وكل من تحب،
into gifts just for you.
إلى هدايا مخصصة لك فقط.
The Buddha is you, the Rakshasa is you.
بوذا هو أنت، وراكشاسا هو أنت.
Victory!
انتصار!
Nameless Rookie has won.
لقد فاز المبتدئ المجهول.
(Train Station)
(محطة القطار)
Still following me?
هل لازلت تتابعني؟
Until you get on.
حتى تصل إلى هناك.
Until you leave on that train.
حتى تغادر على هذا القطار.
- What? - Songtai.
- ماذا؟ - سونغتاي.
Songtai!
سونغتاي!
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Everyone, make way.
الجميع، افسحوا الطريق.
Move aside.
تنحى جانبا.
Chief Wang,
الرئيس وانغ،
I'll be straight with you.
سأكون صريحا معك.
I came despite being hunted.
لقد جئت رغم أنني مطارد.
People like us, pushed aside,
الناس مثلنا، تم دفعهم جانبا،
should join forces,
ينبغي أن توحد القوى،
and find the truth together.
والعثور على الحقيقة معًا.
What do you say?
ماذا تقول؟
Impressive for someone so young.
مُثير للإعجاب لشخص صغير السن.
But I got suspended.
ولكن تم إيقافي.
This matter...
هذا الأمر...
I can't help much.
لا أستطيع المساعدة كثيرا.
I looked into you.
لقد نظرت إليك.
I know.
أنا أعرف.
You're not some rigid fool.
أنت لست أحمقًا متشددًا.
Oh, you checked on me?
أوه، هل قمت بفحصي؟
I did some digging on you too.
لقد قمت ببعض الحفر عليك أيضًا.
The junior officer on loan.
الضابط الصغير المعار.
Your resume is a bit too fictional.
سيرتك الذاتية خيالية بعض الشيء.
You're too suspicious
أنت مشبوه للغاية
I just can't stand leaving
لا أستطيع أن أتحمل المغادرة
without the truth.
بدون الحقيقة.
Besides,
بجانب،
I have an offer you can't turn down.
لدي عرض لا يمكنك رفضه.
Each backup phone I own
كل هاتف احتياطي أملكه
has its own unique contact number.
لديه رقم اتصال فريد خاص به.
I'm warning you,
انا احذرك
don't talk nonsense to Han Xu.
لا تتحدث هراء مع هان شو.
Dr. Chen already said,
لقد قال الدكتور تشين بالفعل،
if he gets agitated,
إذا انزعج،
he'll lose rationality.
سوف يفقد عقلانيته
Relax.
يستريح.
I don't want Chief Han hurt either.
أنا لا أريد أن أتعرض للأذى رئيس هان أيضًا.
So,
لذا،
I need you
أنا بحاجة إليك
and your team.
وفريقك.
Eat first.
تناول الطعام أولا.
I'm skipping the meal.
أنا أتخطى وجبة الطعام.
Might be poisoned.
ربما يكون مسموما.
And you?
وأنت؟
I don't trust either.
أنا لا أثق بأي منهما.
I've been waiting for your call.
لقد كنت أنتظر مكالمتك.
Master.
يتقن.
Chief Han.
الرئيس هان.
I'm not your enemy.
أنا لست عدوك.
But not my friend either.
ولكن ليس صديقي أيضًا.
Let's meet up.
دعونا نلتقي.
I can help you.
أستطيع مساعدتك.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Same place as before.
نفس المكان كما في السابق.
Eight tonight.
الثامنة الليلة.
I hope what I see this time
أتمنى ما أراه هذه المرة
isn't a dead body.
ليست جثة.
(Wu; could be fake)
(وو؛ قد يكون مزيفًا)
I'll ask questions.
سأطرح الأسئلة.
Just answer me.
فقط أجبني.
Leave out anything extra.
اترك أي شيء إضافي.
You're not the real Wu.
أنت لست وو الحقيقي.
Who are you?
من أنت؟
I'm on loan,
أنا على سبيل الإعارة
a police officer on the case.
ضابط شرطة على القضية.
My name's Songtai.
اسمي سونغتاي.
An Shaocong, Xiao Ran,
آن شاوكونغ، شياو ران،
and the real Wu
و وو الحقيقي
died two months ago, right?
مات منذ شهرين، أليس كذلك؟
- Yes. - What are you acting for?
- نعم. - لماذا تتصرف؟
The station's plan.
مخطط المحطة.
Case reenactment.
إعادة تمثيل القضية.
The goal was to trigger you
وكان الهدف هو تحفيزك
to help you recover memories.
لمساعدتك على استعادة الذكريات.
But now the plan
ولكن الآن الخطة
has failed.
لقد فشلت.
So you're saying,
لذا أنت تقول،
Xiao Ran and An Shaocong
شياو ران وآن شاوكونغ
weren't killed by me?
لم يقتلوا من قبلي؟
Then who actually did it?
إذن من الذي فعل ذلك فعليا؟
I'm warning you.
انا احذرك.
Don't talk nonsense to Han Xu.
لا تتحدث هراء مع هان شو.
I have no idea.
ليس لدي أي فكرة.
Let me ask you again.
دعني أسألك مرة أخرى.
Is this tied to Wang Mingcheng?
هل هذا مرتبط بـ وانغ مينغ تشنغ؟
I don't know either.
انا أيضا لا اعرف.
If I didn't kill them,
لو لم أقتلهم،
why are they after me?
لماذا هم بعدي؟
Chief Ma
رئيس ما
pinned the deaths of Zhang Ahua
تم تثبيت وفاة تشانغ أهوا
and the guard on you.
والحارس عليك.
The plan hit a snag.
لقد واجهت الخطة عقبة.
Inside the station,
داخل المحطة،
someone's taking you down.
شخص ما يأخذك إلى الأسفل.
What about Room 405?
ماذا عن الغرفة 405؟
I found nothing.
لم أجد شيئا.
But during the investigation,
ولكن أثناء التحقيق،
I came across something odd.
لقد وجدت شيئا غريبا.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
Xiao Ran.
شياو ران.
She's not really your wife.
إنها ليست زوجتك حقا.
Xu.
شو.
When are we breaking out?
متى سننطلق؟
I'm taking Ran with me.
سآخذ ران معي.
I know a way to get out.
أعرف طريقة للخروج.
I'm ready to deal with Xiao Ran.
أنا مستعد للتعامل مع شياو ران.
Your wife Xiao Ran is gone too.
زوجتك شياو ران رحلت أيضًا.
Only the dead pose no threat.
الموتى فقط هم من لا يشكلون أي تهديد.
Xu!
شو!
I know
أنا أعرف
it's hard for you to digest,
من الصعب عليك هضمه،
but it's the truth.
ولكنها الحقيقة.
You're still lying!
أنت لا تزال تكذب!
♪Waiting for the fragrance of flowers♪
♪في انتظار عطر الزهور♪
♪To cross over the high wall♪
♪لتجاوز الجدار العالي♪
♪Waiting for the shore♪
♪في انتظار الشاطئ♪
♪To forget the storm♪
♪لنسيان العاصفة♪
♪Just like this♪
♪تماما مثل هذا♪
♪Wasting a few inches♪
♪إهدار بضع بوصات♪
♪Of daylight♪
♪من ضوء النهار♪
♪Half for the memories♪
♪نصف للذكريات♪
♪Half for the dreams♪
♪نصف للأحلام♪
♪Oh, little boat♪
♪أوه، قارب صغير♪
♪Where are you going♪
♪إلى أين أنت ذاهب♪
♪No need to answer that♪
♪لا داعي للإجابة على ذلك♪
♪Just let me♪
♪فقط دعني♪
♪Watch you drift away♪
♪شاهدك تبتعد♪
♪Into the sunset glow♪
♪في ضوء غروب الشمس♪
♪Don't be afraid♪
♪لا تخف♪
♪This world♪
♪هذا العالم♪
♪Is vast as it may be♪
♪إنه واسع كما قد يكون♪
♪But there's always♪
♪ولكن هناك دائما♪
♪Someone who cares♪
♪شخص يهتم♪
♪Shining like a lighthouse♪
♪متألق مثل المنارة♪